# Evy M. Haan

## Content Designer

evy-content.design | linkedin.com/in/evyhaan evy.haan@gmail.com | Seattle, WA

#### Objective

While working as a software engineer focused on frontend development, I discovered a passion for using thoughtful language to connect with people, ease friction of using technology, and create more human user experiences. I completed a professional certification in UX Writing toward pursuing new opportunities in the content design field.

#### **Highlighted Projects**

UX Writer, Student | Handshake App

Jan 2022

- Developed content strategy deliverables for a fictional business management application
- Conducted a competitor analysis
- Developed a product persona, voice and tone schematics, and a style guide
- Documented design decisions, versioning, and maintained a project board

### **Professional Experience**

Software Development Engineer II | Xevo Inc.

Nov 2019 - Jul 2021

- Developed user-interface features on a connected-car infotainment platform (Kotlin, Java, JavaScript)
- Collaborated with Product Managers, Designers, Engineers, and QA
- Participated in design implementation strategy and limitation discussions, ticket grooming, and code reviews
- Contributed to a library of reusable UI components that helped UI/UX consistency, maintainability, and efficiency
- Documented custom UI component description and usage
- Added multi-branch ci/cd pipelines to enable feature testing and validation
- Learned workflow tools, frameworks, and languages while contributing to ongoing app and library development
- Worked in a fast-paced, highly-iterative timeline to deliver customized demos on tight deadlines

Software Engineer, Contract | DashBento

Aug 2019 – Dec 2019

- Participated in user story creation, feature development, and code review on a remote team
- Developed front-end components and relational database models (React, Python)

Executive Assistant | Pioneer Human Services

Feb 2018 - Oct 2018

- Previewed documents, compiled reports, facilitated scheduling for the department VP
- Worked with cross-divisional and cross-discipline teams to meet competing deadlines

Administrative Assistant | Pioneer Human Services

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

- Liaised on-the-ground details for the International Community Corrections Association annual conference
- Managed corporate files including 65+ vehicles, 250+ drivers, and archives for 20+ unique programs
- Implemented employee recognition rewards program for 1000+ state-wide employees
- Assisted admin team in supporting clients exiting incarceration, company employees, VPs, and C-level managers

Supported Employment Specialist | Trillium Employment Services

Nov 2014 - Oct 2015

- Discussed disability employment with community businesses
- Created and conducted vocational skill & interest assessments
- Coached a caseload of 8-12 clients in interview preparation
- Communicated goals & progress reports with clients, supervisors, guardians, and case managers

#### **Tools**

Figma, Adobe XD, Google Docs, Cloudinary, Jira, Confluence, HTML, CSS, Git, Miro, Android Studio, VS Code

#### Education

Certificate in Fundamentals of UX Writing   UX Content Collective   Remote	2022
Advanced Software Development Certificate   Code Fellows   Seattle, WA	2019
Community Health Education, BS   Western Washington University   Bellingham, WA	2013
Minors: Psychology, Communication	